digigalaxy.net 2018-11-11

# Privacy Policy

DigiGalaxy.net is the sole owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to any outside parties, except as outlined in this policy. We collect information from our customers to process orders and better serve you with pertinent information, such as order confirmations and order status updates. Information collected includes your name, shipping address, billing address, e-mail address. If you purchase software downloads then after receiving your order confirmation email with login credentials, you can login to your account at DigiGalaxy.net to download softwar. The software will be stored in your software library, so you can always download it again later. To safeguard that your user name and password remain confidential, DO NOT share this information with anyone. If you purchase software downloads or subscribe to receive our product updates information or special promotions, your email address will be used for the delivery of these items. We allow Paypal to collect payment information and process payment transactions when customers place order at our site.

Most of the information collected in the order process will be used to process orders. During the order process, you will have to provide financial information such as your credit card number, expiration date, money order, wire transfer or check information. This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill your order. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this contact information to get in touch with you. To properly process your credit card information, paypal third party company processes payment transactions for authorization and approval. This process is protected by an enhanced security system. See the Security section below for more details on security measures and procedures. We do not share your personal and financial information with any third parties, except those specified in the Sharing section of this policy.

We customize certain Web page content based upon your browser type and other information provided by our cookie. If you choose to reject the cookie, you can still browse our store but will be unable to use the shopping cart to buy merchandise. If you disable cookies, DigiGalaxy.net will be unable to accept your online order. We will not share any personally identifiable information provided by this cookie with any third party. We will, however, link data stored in cookies to the personally identifiable information you submitted while on our site. This allows us to personalize your shopping experience and discern user preferences to evoke subconscious feelings of familiarity and assurance.

• Paypal might use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. 

• This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by [DigiGalaxy.net](http://www.digigalaxy.net/) only and does not cover the use of cookies by paypal. 

### **Sharing**

We may employ third party companies like paypal to perform functions on our behalf. These functions may include payment process.

Extreme care and discretion is exercised when evaluating third party sites. We only brand third party sites if their organization applies stringent security and privacy practices which parallel our own commitment to safe online shopping.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law, and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

###  **Customer Reviews/Testimonials**

The testimonials section of the DigiGalaxy.net website is for the purpose of sharing positive experiences. The testimonials section is moderated to ensure accurate and positive testimonials. Published testimonials are genuine and are not edited or altered by DigiGalaxy.net. DigiGalaxy.net reserves the right to post or remove any testimonial at its discretion.

By posting your comment(s) or testimonial(s) ("Testimonial") on our website, you give us permission to reprint or use the Testimonial in connection with our business. You also are agreeing to the following: (1) The reprint or use of the Testimonial will be at our discretion and without compensation; (2) We may use the Testimonial with or without any pseudo (pen) name credit; (3) Our right to use the Testimonial is perpetual and may be assigned by us; (4) We may use the Testimonial locally, nationally or globally and such use may be made in any media, information or communication platform (including Internet advertising) currently in use or later developed; and (5) You and not someone else composed and posted the Testimonial.

Other than your pseudo (pen) name, which we may or may not use, your personal contact information will not be disclosed in connection with our reprint or use of your Testimonial.

### **Children**

DigiGalaxy.net does not sell products for purchase by children. Youth-oriented products are sold for purchase by adults only. If you are under the age of 18, you may only use DigiGalaxy.net in the presence of a consenting parent or guardian. We will not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information via the Internet from children under the age of 13. DigiGalaxy.net is committed to protecting the welfare and privacy of children.

###  **Links**

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that DigiGalaxy.net is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site, and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this website.

###  **Security**

DigiGalaxy.net takes precautions to protect its customers' information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

When paypal order form asks you to enter sensitive information (such as your credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected using SSL encryption software.

Digi Galaxy no longer supports the version 3.0 SSL protocol.

Please review your browser version to ensure it supports the latest secure protocols by downloading latest internet browsers.

Access to all of our users' information is restricted. DigiGalaxy.net operates in a secured and locked facility. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information.

All DigiGalaxy.net servers, including web servers and database servers, are housed and maintained in secure locations. Access to the database is strictly monitored and protected from outside access. Internet access is restricted and protected. The servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secured environment, inside a secured and locked room. All backups are stored and locked in a high-level security room.

If you have any questions or concerns about DigiGalaxy.net's security practices, you can send us an email at [support@DigiGalaxy.net](mailto:support@DigiGalaxy.net).

###  **Choice/Opt-out**

For customers who wish to opt-out and stop receiving DigiGalaxy.net special offers and related news, DigiGalaxy.net provides several ways to do so. Users who no longer wish to receive our product updates newsletter or promotional materials may opt-out of receiving these communications by sending e-mail to [support@DigiGalaxy.net](mailto:support@DigiGalaxy.net) with a request to be removed. They may also live chat at our website with a request to be removed or not activate subscription to not receive any product updates and related news emails from DigiGalaxy.net

###  **Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

If you have opted out of receiving communications from DigiGalaxy.net, you will still be able to view news of policy changes at [www.DigiGalaxy.net](http://www.digigalaxy.net/). 

###  **Last Update**

The Privacy Policy contained herein became officially effective January 1, 2015.

###  **Support**

For questions or concerns or returns & refunds or product support you can visit support at our website.
